We're talking about scheduling and working from a home office.
And how to use your time, efficiently.
A lot of people have, who work from home offices, myself included.
Have found that it's very helpful if you set up a routine or a schedule.
While you're working at home.
And that kind of, keeps you from just getting too scattered.
And either working too much or too little.
To just kind of, you know, space your time out.
For me, what works well is I have, I use my Google calendar.
Now that isn't always true.
And it depends on the work you're doing.
We all do different types of work from a home office.
Some of us are running eBay business or writer like myself.
Or maybe a computer programmer or a graphic artist.
Whatever you do.
You know, but for the most part, we can kind of.
We kind of, know how long our job's are going to take.
So it's nice to kind of, pace out and schedule.
Especially if it's a job that's due, down the road.
So we'll talk about how to kind of, take your projects.
And how to space them out to make sure they get done by deadlines.
We'll talk about deadlines, next.